https://www.viacomprivacy.com#web

HOME
CA Do Not Sell My Info
ACCESS AND DELETION REQUEST
WELCOME TO THE VIACOM DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS CENTER!
Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), California residents have the right to request access to or deletion of their personal information, to request additional details about our information practices, to opt out of the "sale" of their personal information, and to not be discriminated against for exercising these rights. Below we explain how you may exercise these rights.
Access and Deletion Request Instructions
To submit a Data Access or Deletion Request, please click Data Requests Submission and it will take you directly to the Data Request Submission page in order for you to submit your Request.
Do Not Sell My Information Instructions
At Viacom, we will never sell any information that identifies you personally like your name, email address, or phone number. We do work with advertising partners who use cookies and device identifiers as described in our Privacy Policy to show ads that are targeted to your interests. Some of these disclosures may be considered sales under California law. You may opt out of these disclosures by following the instructions below. Please note that if you use a different browser or device to access a Viacom website or mobile or online application, or if you visit a different Viacom property, you will need to renew this choice and will need to opt out separately on each website and device.
Websites:
To opt out of the disclosure of your personal information associated with your browser or device from a Viacom website, you may do so by using the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") CCPA Tool. The DAA offers an Ad Choices tool, adapted specifically for the "Do Not Sell My Personal Info" right under the California Consumer Privacy Act 2019, which offers a centralized place to opt out of the sale of personal information by any or all DAA participating businesses that are collecting your personal information across multiple websites. To exercise your right to opt out of the sale of your personal information for use in interest-based advertising by these third parties, click on the icon below.
Please visit http://srp.viacom.com/sitefaq.html for more information on the key third-party partners that we use to provide online behavioral advertising, sometimes called personalized advertising or tailored advertising and your choices regarding the use of your information for those purposes.
Mobile and Online Applications
To opt out of allowing our advertising partners to use information about your app usage to show you personalized ads on your mobile or connected tv device, please follow the instructions below:
Amazon Fire Tablet:
Navigate to Settings > Security & Privacy > Advertising ID and disable the "Interest-based Ads" option, which when enabled, allows apps to use your advertising ID to build profiles or show you interest-based ads.
Android Phone/Tablet:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Privacy' > 'Ads' and enable "Opt out of Ads Personalization" and select "Reset Advertising ID"
Android TV:
Navigate to https://adssettings.google.com/ to turn it off for associated Google Accounts.
Additional on-device options may be available for =< Android OS 7.x devices, however the above mentioned will turn it off universally.
For Sony TV: Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Network' > 'Samba Interactive TV' > "Disable/Off"
Amazon Fire TV:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Preferences' > 'Privacy' and disable "Interest Based Ads" and select "Reset Advertising ID"
Apple Phone/Tablet:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Privacy' > 'Advertising' and enable "Limit Ad Tracking" and select "Reset Advertising Identifier..."
AppleTV:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'General' > 'Privacy' > 'Advertising' and enable "Limit Ad Tracking" and select "Reset advertising Identifier"
Catalyst:
Navigate to the 'Apple menu' > 'System Preferences' > 'Security & Privacy' > 'Privacy' and enable "Limit Ad Tracking" and select "Reset Advertising Identifier"
Oculus:
Open the Oculus app on your phone > Tap 'More' > 'Privacy Settings'
Hisense:
Visit Hisense's privacy page for more information on how to opt-out > https://app.cookiepro.com/app/#/webform/b861842b-f225-4fcc-afcc-2b5930c9c2a2
Roku:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Privacy' > 'Advertising' and enable "Limit Ad Tracking" and select "Reset Advertising Identifier..."
Samsung TV:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Support' > 'Terms & Policy' > "Internet Based Advertising" > and deselect "Enable to make the content and advertising on Smart TV more interactive."
Vizio TV:
Navigate to 'HDTV Settings app' > 'System' > 'Reset & Admin' > Highlight 'Viewing Data' > Press right arrow to change the setting to "Off"
X1 Set Top Box (Contour):
Requires sign-in with their cable provider. Visit https://www.cox.com/residential/support/opting-out-of-location-based-advertising.html for more information.
X1 Set / X1 Flex:
Requires sign-in with their cable provider. Visit https://www.xfinity.com/adservices for more information.
Xbox 360:
Navigate to 'System' > 'Settings' > 'Account' > 'Privacy and Online Safety' > 'App Privacy' > 'General' > deselect "Enable Advertising ID"
Xbox One / HTML 5:
Navigate to 'Settings' > 'Account > 'Privacy & Online Safety' > 'App privacy' > 'General' and check to ensure that "Enable Advertising Identifier" is disabled.
If you need further assistance regarding your rights, please contact us at Privacy@viacom.com, and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.
VIACOMPRIVACY.COM
